sugabit.net 2016-02-02

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to sugabit.net websites, services, applications and other products that link to this privacy policy. sugabit.net is committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information sugabit.net may gather about individuals who interact with sugabit.net, how that information is used, and sugabit.net's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to sugabit.net products, and not to the sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from our products.

### Information Collection.

sugabit.net may collect anonymous information when you interact with us so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type.  
The sugabit.net products do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, for you to use the product. The products assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the product, your search terms, and the links upon which you click. We use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. sugabit.net analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Information Use.

The information we collect is used by us to improve our products, offer you more relevant search results and ads, protect our users and products, and identify and block malicious uses of our products. If you contact sugabit.net, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your e-mail address.

### Third Party Information Gathering.

The products include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy.

The products contain links to other sites. Please be aware that sugabit.net is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by sugabit.net products.

### Cookies.

sugabit.net may set and access sugabit.net or third party cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on the sugabit.net products our visitors view and which browsers or devices our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you within various products in a way that may be linked to individual user information you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site.

We also engage third party ad networks that may place cookies on your device when accessing and using our products that collect anonymous, non-personal information regarding your access and use. This information may be used by sugabit.net and its third party ad network partners to identify and target related advertising to the user of such computer, when on our sites within the third party’s advertising network of sites. For information about opting-out of third party ad network cookies, please see the opt-out section below.

### Sharing.

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on us. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of sugabit.net's or such product's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

Products may use third party service providers to serve ads, search listings, and other information. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness and use information so we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation.

### Mergers; Business Transitions.

In the event sugabit.net goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### Notification of Changes.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, however, we are going to use Individually Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our site for 30 days.

Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Users under the age of 13). We do not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13; or knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 with third parties.

It is possible that we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information.
